Finding aid to Buildings records CA.MS.00104
Smith College Archives
- Jordan House
  - -Bookplate
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1922-1990; undated (Box 218, Folder 20)
  - -Photographs-Interior, 1922 (Box 218, Folder 21)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1922-1995; undated (Box 218, Folder 22)
- Jordan House Annex (7 Paradise Road), 1920 (Box 218, Folder 23)
- Juniper Lodge
  - -General Histories, 1950 &amp; 1957 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - -Brochures, 1955-1979; undated (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - -Chocorua Lake Area
    - -General, 1965 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - -Chocorua Lake Association, undated (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - -Legends, undated (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - -New Hampshire Smith Club, 1948-1961 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - -Relocation of Route 16, 1950 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - -Committee Reports, Notes, and Minutes, 1924-1964 (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - -Committee Reports, Notes, and Minutes, 1965-1980 (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - -Correspondence
    - -General, 1923-1924 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - -General, 1925-1926 (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - -General, 1927-1929 (Box 219, Folder 12)
    - -General, 1940-1949 (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - -General, 1950-1951 (Box 219, Folder 14)
    - -General, 1952-1953 (Box 219, Folder 15)
    - -General, 1954-1955 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - -General, 1956-1957 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - -General, 1958-1959 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - -General, 1960-1961 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - -General, 1962-1964 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - -General, 1965 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - -General, 1966 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - -General, 1967-1980 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - -General, undated (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - -Letter From Otelia Cromwell '00, 1951 (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - -Yale, 1924-1929 (Box 220.1, Folder 1)
    - -Yale, 1947-1978 (Box 220.1, Folder 2)
  - -Establishment
    - -General, 1919-1923; 1975 (Box 220.1, Folder 3)
    - -Reynolds, James Bronson, 1883-1891 (Box 220.1, Folder 4)
    - -Reynolds, James Bronson-Correspondence, 1923 (Box 220.1, Folder 5)
  - -Finances, 1924-1929 (Box 220.1, Folder 6)
  - -Finances, 1946-1962 (Box 220.1, Folder 7)
  - -Finances, 1963-1979 (Box 220.1, Folder 8)
  - -Finances-Budd Bequest, 1965 (Box 220.1, Folder 9)
  - -Finances-Early Fundraising, 1924-1925 (Box 220.1, Folder 10)
  - -Finances-Early Fundraising-Records of Contribution, 1924-1925 (Box 220.1, Folder 11)
  - -Forms, 1952-1977 (Box 220.1, Folder 12)
  - -Guests
    - -Applications for Reservation and Fellowship, 1947 (Box 220.1, Folder 13)
    - -Eligibility Requirements, 1923-1977 (Box 220.1, Folder 14)
    - -Guest Book, 1924-1931 (Box 220.2, Folder 1)
    - -Guest Book, 1931-1979
      [see Oversize Box 10 (Appendix H)]
    - -Fellowship Certificates, 1957-1967 (Box 220.2, Folder 2)
    - -Records of Payment, 1942-1964 (Box 220.2, Folder 3)
    - -Residence Charts, 1924-1966; undated (Box 220.2, Folder 4)
    - -Residence, Fellowship, and Application Lists, 1924-1967; undated (Box 220.2, Folder 5)
  - -Inventories (Furniture, Silver, etca.), 1929-1980; undated (Box 220.2, Folder 6)
  - -Maintenance and Supplies, 1925-1974 (Box 220.2, Folder 7)
  - -Maps, 1937-1962 (Box 220.2, Folder 8)
  - -Notices of Opening and Availability, 1925-1979 (Box 220.2, Folder 9)
  - -Operations, 1924-1966; undated (Box 220.3, Folder 1)
  - -Personnel-Committee Appointments, 1924-1968 (Box 220.3, Folder 2)
  - -Personnel-Lodge Staff, 1924-1973 (Box 220.3, Folder 3)
  - -Press Releases and Clippings, 1924-1981 (Box 220.3, Folder 4)
  - -Press Releases and Clippings-Air Bulletin, 1948 (Box 220.3, Folder 5)
  - -Sale and Closing, 1980 (Box 220.3, Folder 6)
  - -Writings About the Lodge, 1924-1925 (Box 220.3, Folder 7)
  - -Miscellaneous
    - -Postcard, oversize, undated (Box 220.3, Folder 8)
    - -Signs, undated (Box 220.3, Folder 9)
    - -Signs
    - -Stationery, 1962; undated (Box 220.3, Folder 10)
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1925-1970; undated (Box 220.3, Folder 11)
  - -Photographs-Exterior-Porch, 1924-1970; undated (Box 220.3, Folder 12)
  - -Photographs-Exterior-Views From the Lodge, 1934-1970; undated (Box 220.3, Folder 13)
  - -Photographs-Interior, undated (Box 220.3, Folder 14)
  - -Photographs-Groups, undated (Box 220.3, Folder 15)
- Kneeland Home
  [see President's House]
- Lamont House
  - -General, 1955- (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - -Bookplate
  - -Christmas Party, 1959 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - -Julie's Quilt, 1991-1993 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - -Photographs (Box 221)
    - -Exterior, 1954- (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - -Interior, 1950- (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - -Groups, 1955- (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - -Groups (Box 221)
      [see also Oversize Box 12 (Appendix H)]
- Lapan Inn
  [see Green Street # 30]
- Laundry (College Lane and State Street), 1905-1992 (Box 221, Folder 7)
- Laundry-Laundry Lists, 1894-1975 (Box 221, Folder 8)
- Laura Scales House
  [see also Franklin King House and see also Quadrangle]
  - -General, 1935- (Box 221, Folder 9)
  - -Anniversaries, 1956-1961 (Box 221, Folder 10)
  - -Artifacts
  - -Murals, 1936-1979 (Box 221, Folder 11)
  - -Photographs (Box 221)
    - -Exterior, 1936- (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - -Interior, 1936; undated (Box 221.1, Folder 1)
    - -Groups, 1937-1952 (Box 221.1, Folder 2)
    - -Groups, 1953- (Box 221.1, Folder 3)
    - -Groups (Box 221.1)
- Laura Scales and Franklin King Houses-Photographs-Exterior, 1935- (Box 221.1, Folder 4)
- Laura Scales and Franklin King Houses-Sketches and Drawings (Arch.), 1930 (Box 221.1, Folder 5)
- Lawrence House
  - -General, 1904- (Box 221.1, Folder 6)
  - -History, 1912-1923 (Box 221.1, Folder 7)
  - -History, 1933-1951 (Box 221.1, Folder 8)
  - -Anniversaries, 1942 (Box 221.1, Folder 9)
  - -Artifacts
  - -Correspondence with Elizabeth Lawrence Clarke 1883, 1913 (Box 221.1, Folder 10)
  - -Head of House Notebook, 1952 (Box 221.1, Folder 11)
  - -House Library
    [see Libraries-House-Lawrence]
  - -House President's Notebook, 1913 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - -Memory Book Presented to Julia Caverno, 1922-1923 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - -Roster / Register, 1922-1968 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - -Roster / Register, 1981-1982 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - -Photographs (Box 222)
    - -Exterior, 1892- (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - -Interior, 1895- (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - -Groups, 1898- (Box 222, Folder 7)
- Libraries
  - -General, 1968-1993; undated (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - -Histories
    - -General, 1875-1994 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - -History of the Library at Smith College by M. Anderson, 1975-1910 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - -The History of the Foundation and Development of the Smith College Library by M. Grierson 1922, 1874-1917 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - -The History of the Foundation Cont'd, 1917-1920 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - -Bibliographies and Reference Guides, 1983; undated (Box 223, Folder 6)
    [see also Libraries-WANL-Bibliographies and Reference Guides]
  - -Bookplates
    [see Appendix C for item-level list of bookplates]
    - -General, undated (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - -Branch and Specialty Libraries, undated (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - -Department Libraries, undated (Box 223, Folder 9)
      [see also Libraries-Department Libraries]
    - -House Libraries, undated (Box 223, Folder 10)
      [see also Libraries-House Libraries]
    - -William Allan Neilson Library
      - -General, undated (Box 223, Folder 11)
      - -Groups, undated (Box 223, Folder 12)
      - -Individuals-A-B, undated (Box 223, Folder 13)
      - -Individuals-Abbott, Senda Berenson, 1930 (Box 223, Folder 14)
      - -Individuals-C, undated (Box 223, Folder 15)
      - -Individuals-Comstock, Ada Louise 1897, 1980 (Box 223, Folder 16)
      - -Individuals-D-G, undated (Box 223, Folder 17)
      - -Individuals-H-L, undated (Box 223, Folder 18)
      - -Individuals-M-O, undated (Box 223, Folder 19)
      - -Individuals-P, undated (Box 223, Folder 20)
      - -Individuals-Putnam, Karl Scott, 1966 (Box 223, Folder 21)
      - -Individuals-Q-V, undated (Box 223, Folder 22)
      - -Individuals-Seelye, L. Clark, 1901 (Box 223, Folder 23)
      - -Individuals-W-Z, undated (Box 223, Folder 24)
      - -Miscellaneous, undated (Box 223, Folder 25)
  - -Clarke Library (Memorial Hall), 1875-1879 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - -College Hall Library, 1880-1900; 1974 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - -Department Libraries-General, 1912-1977 (Box 224, Folder 3)
    [see also Libraries-Bookplates-Department Libraries]
  - -Department Libraries-Philosophy-Phelps Memorial Asso., 1883-1894 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - -Friends of the Library
    - -Annual Meetings and Lectures, 1948- (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - -Annual Reports, 1942-1970 (Box 224)
      [see Bound Copies]
    - -Annual Reports, 1970-1979 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - -Annual Reports, 1980-1983 (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - -Brochures and Pamphlets, 1981-1989; undated (Box 224, Folder 8)
    - -Correspondence
      - -General, 1952- (Box 225, Folder 1)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1945 (Box 225, Folder 2)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1950 (Box 225, Folder 3)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1951 (Box 225, Folder 4)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1952 (Box 225, Folder 5)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1953 (Box 225, Folder 6)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1954 (Box 225, Folder 7)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1955 (Box 225, Folder 8)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1956 (Box 225, Folder 9)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1957 (Box 225, Folder 10)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 11)
      - -M. Grierson to Mrs. Patch, 1959 (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - -Council Reports Notes, and Minutes, 1945-1955 (Box 225, Folder 13)
    - -Council Reports, Notes, and Minutes, 1956- (Box 225, Folder 14)
    - -Events, 1966- (Box 225, Folder 15)
    - -Events-Keepsakes, 1979- (Box 225, Folder 16)
      [see Appendix A for item-level list of keepsakes]
    - -Founding and Organization, 1934-1944 (Box 225, Folder 17)
    - -Newsletter, 1971-1996 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - -Newsletter, 1997- (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - -Office Furnishings, 1983 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - -Publication Schedules and Budgets, 1972 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - -Publications
      - -General, 1963-1970 (Box 226)
      - -Essays
        - -Henry James in Northampton by Dean Flower, 1971 (Box 226, Folder 5)
        - -Mishaps of a Compulsive Collector by Philip Hofer, 1970 (Box 226, Folder 6)
        - -Two Aspects of Memory (Collecting for Scholars by F. Adams, Jr. and The Task of Recollection by G. Piel), 1968 (Box 226, Folder 7)
      - -Keepsakes
        [see Events-Keepsakes]
      - -Rare Book Room-The Landscape Alphabet, 1981 (Box 226, Folder 8)
      - -SSC-Unpublished Papers Series, Booklets 1-4, 1963-1966 (Box 226, Folder 9)
      - -SSC-Unpublished Papers Series, Booklets 5-8, 1967-1970 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - -Sophia Smith Collection, 1945-1970 (Box 226, Folder 11)
      [see also Council Reports, Notes, and Minutes]
    - -Photographs (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - Libraries-Friends of the Library-Annual Reports 1-10 (Bound), 1942-1952 (Box 224.1)
    - Libraries-Friends of the Library-Annual Reports 11-20 (Bound), 1953-1962 (Box 224.1)
    - Libraries-Friends of the Library-Annual Reports 21-25 (Bound), 1963-1970 (Box 224.2)
    - Libraries-Friends of the Library-Friends of the Library Publications (Bound), 1963-1967 (Box 224.2)
    - Libraries-Friends of the Library-Friends of the Library Publications (Bound), 1968-1970 (Box 224.1)
  - -Hillyer Art Library
    - Annual Reports & Statistics of Art Librarian, 1957-2008; 2018-A-0056; 1 linear feet (2 full document boxes); 4 items (4 CDs) (Box 116, Box 117)
      Scope and Contents
      Annual reports, financial information, and memoranda related to the operations of the Hillyer Art Library, to the College Librarian.
      CDs
      - CD, "New Hillyer", 2002 Aug 21; 2 items (2 copies of the same CD) (Box 117)
      - CD, "Hillyer Rededication" copy and master, 2003; 2 items (2 CDs) (Box 117)
    - -General, 1968- (Box 226, Folder 13)
    - -Bibliographies, 1963-1984 (Box 226, Folder 14)
    - -Bookplate
    - -Photographs, 1933- (Box 226, Folder 15)
  - -House Libraries
    [see also Libraries-Bookplates-House Libraries]
    - -General, 1944-1978 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - -Cushing House, 1927 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - -Hatfield House, 1889 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - -Lawrence House, 1938 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - -Martha Wilson House, 1945 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - -Tyler House, 1962 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - -Washburn House (Box 227, Folder 6a)
  - -Interlibrary Exchanges
    - -General, 1967- (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - -Books and Libraries by Flora Ludington, 1955-56 (Box 227, Folder 8)
    - -Five-College Library System (Box 227)
      [see 70. Intercollegiate-Five Colleges-F-N]
    - -Forbes Library, 1961; undated (Box 227, Folder 9)
      [see also Libraries-Histories]
    - -Hampshire Interlibrary Center (HILC)
      - -General, 1947-1950 (Box 227, Folder 10)
      - -General, 1951-1959 (Box 227, Folder 11)
      - -General, 1960-1976 (Box 227, Folder 12)
      - -Annual Reports, 1951-1967 (Box 227, Folder 13)
      - -Cresap, McCormick, and Paget Survey, 1954 (Box 227, Folder 14)
      - -Metcalf Survey, 1957 (Box 227, Folder 15)
    - -New England College Librarians' Association, 1908-1945; undated (Box 227, Folder 16)
  - -Loan Library (Davis Student Center), undated (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - -Memorial Funds, 1963-1965 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - -Music Library
    [see Libraries-Sage Hall Library and Libraries-Werner Josten Performing Arts Library]
  - -Newsletter News From the Libraries, 1987- (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - -Policy
    - -Circulation, 1947- (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - -Circulation-Non-Smith Borrowers, 1998 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - -Graffiti, 1942 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - -Reserve Books, 1937-1989 (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - -Reports and Surveys, 1969 (Box 228, Folder 8)
  - -Sabin-Reed Science Library
    - -General, 1960-1976; undated (Box 228, Folder 9)
    - -Library Reports from Biology Department, 1971-1977 (Box 228, Folder 10)
    - -Photographs, 1934-1990; undated (Box 228, Folder 11)
  - -Sage Hall Library, 1940-1965; undated (Box 228, Folder 12)
  - -Seelye Hall Library
    - -General, 1900-1909 (Box 228, Folder 13)
    - -Shelf Diagrams
    - -Photographs, 1900-1909 (Box 228, Folder 14)
  - -Staff
    - -General, 1909- (Box 228, Folder 15)
    - -Cookbook-The Eater's Guide, 1982 (Box 228, Folder 16)
  - Libraries-Newsletter News from the Libraries (Bound), 1987-2001 (Box 228)
  - -Staff
    - -Cookbook-The Eater's Guide Originals pp. 1-65, 1982 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - -Cookbook-The Eater's Guide Originals pp. 66-117, 1982 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - -Glossary of Library Terms for Employees, 1986 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - -Library Staff Association, 1987- (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - -Meeting Minutes, 1908-1911 (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - -Meeting Minutes, 1912-1919 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - -Parties, 1946- (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - -Staff Council Activities Committee, 1997- (Box 229, Folder 8)
    - -Staff Fund, 1951-1992 (Box 229, Folder 9)
    - -Staff Manual, 1974- (Box 229, Folder 10)
    - -Staff Manual-Outdated Pages, 1981- (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - -Telephone Courtesy Pamphlet, undated (Box 229, Folder 12)
  - -Statistics, 1908-1938 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - -Statistics, 1912-1987; undated (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - -Technical Services, 1971-1977 (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - -Usage Guides, 1953; undated (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - -Usage Guides, 1983-1988; undated (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - -Usage Guides-Faculty, 1987 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - -War Service, 1917-1918 (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - -Werner Josten Performing Arts Library
    - -General, 1968- (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - -Architectural Plans
    - -Bibliographies and Catalogs, 1972-1975; undated (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - -Photographs, 1977-1988; undated (Box 230, Folder 10)
  - -William Allan Neilson Library
    [see Boxes 61-75]
  - -Young Science Library, 1991- (Box 230, Folder 11)
  - -Miscellaneous, undated (Box 230, Folder 12)
  - -Photographs-Slides (List only in folder), 1975 (Box 230, Folder 13)
  - News from the Libraries- Smith College (2 volumes), 1987-2006 (Box 230.1)
  - -William Allan Neilson Library
    - -General, 1962- (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - -Accessions
      [see Boxes 66-73]
    - -Anniversaries, 1934 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - -Anniversaries, 1959 (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - -Anniversaries, 1984 (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - -Architectural Plans
    - -Artworks
      - -General, 1950-1965 (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - -Murals, 1910 (Box 231, Folder 6)
      - -Portraits, 1935-1957 (Box 231, Folder 7)
      - -Sculpture, 1912-1913; undated (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - -Bibliographies and Reference Guides
      - -General, 1931- (Box 231, Folder 9)
      - -Indexes and Abstracts, 1970-1980 (Box 231, Folder 10)
      - -Subjects A-D, 1972-1988 (Box 231, Folder 11)
      - -Subjects E-F, 1976-1986 (Box 231, Folder 12)
      - -Subjects G-Z, 1971-1986 (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - -Browsing Room, 1931-1998; undated (Box 231, Folder 14)
      [see also Libraries-WANL-Furnishings-Browsing Room, see also Libraries-WANL-Correspondence-Chandler, see also Libraries-WANL-Correspondence-Dodd, and see also Libraries-WANL-Correspondence-Eaton]
    - -Carrels, 1939- (Box 231, Folder 15)
    - -Catalogue Department, 1889 (Box 231, Folder 16)
    - -Classes in the Library, 1939 (Box 231, Folder 17)
    - -Construction
      - -Alumnae Gym Complex
        - -General, 1974-1976 (Box 231, Folder 18)
        - -General, 1978-1982 (Box 231, Folder 19)
        - -Feasibility Study-Mitchell, Burditt, and Associates, 1974 (Box 232, Folder 1)
        - -Program Proposal-Mitchell, Burditt, and Associates, 1974 (Box 232, Folder 2)
        - -Program Proposal-Weese, Harry, 1976 (Box 232, Folder 3)
      - -Main Building, 1906-1910 (Box 232, Folder 4)
      - -Main Building-Plans and Specifications, 1908-1909 (Box 232, Folder 5)
      - -North Wing, 1936-1939 (Box 232, Folder 6)
      - -Northwest and South Wings, 1960-1962 (Box 232, Folder 7)
      - -Northwest and South Wings-Floor Plans, 1962 (Box 232, Folder 8)
    - -Correspondence (with Librarian-Incoming and Outgoing)
      - -Andrews, Hannah Dunlop 1904, 1916 (Box 232.1, Folder 1)
      - -Avery, R. Janet Gilfillan 1903, 1909 (Box 232.1, Folder 2)
      - -Baldwin, Sidney 1910, 1914 (Box 232.1, Folder 3)
      - -Blakely, Bertha E., 1910-1916 (Box 232.1, Folder 4)
      - -Brooks, Henrietta St. B., 1910 (Box 232.1, Folder 5)
      - -Burgess, Helen Davis 1895, 1908 (Box 232.1, Folder 6)
      - -Burgess, Laura Crane 1896, 1911 (Box 232.1, Folder 7)
      - -Byers, Harriet Gertrude 1909, undated (Box 232.1, Folder 8)
      - -Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1917 (Box 232.1, Folder 9)
      - -Chandler, Lucie Tower 1905, 1910-1917 (Box 232.1, Folder 10)
      - -Churchill, Alfred Vance, 1918 (Box 232.1, Folder 11)
      - -Clarke, Ellen williston 1885, 1919 (Box 232.1, Folder 12)
      - -Clarke, Elizabeth Lawrence 1883, 1913-1918 (Box 232.1, Folder 13)
      - -Cone, Kate Morris 1879, 1911-1915 (Box 232.1, Folder 14)
      - -Cushman, Alice L., 1910 (Box 232.1, Folder 15)
      - -Dey, Mary Duguid 1884, 1910 (Box 232.1, Folder 16)
      - -Dodd, Marion E., 1909-1914 (Box 232.1, Folder 17)
      - -Dunton, Edith K. 1897, 1908 (Box 232.1, Folder 18)
      - -Eaton, Abby Allen 1899, 1910-1913 (Box 232.1, Folder 19)
      - -Fellows, Helen 1906, 1911 (Box 232.1, Folder 20)
      - -Fletcher, Robert S., 1910-1917 (Box 232.1, Folder 21)
      - -Foley, Margaret Baker 1890, 1918 (Box 232.1, Folder 22)
      - -Furnman, Fannie 1906, 1910 (Box 232.1, Folder 23)
      - -Granger, Edith Hawkes 1891, 1915 (Box 232.1, Folder 24)
      - -Johnston, Dr. W. Dawson, 1910-1916 (Box 232.1, Folder 25)
      - -Kimball, Alfred P., 1911-1912 (Box 232.1, Folder 26)
      - -Lane, William CA., 1915 (Box 232.1, Folder 27)
      - -Pomeroy, Laura Holmes 1908, 1910 (Box 232.1, Folder 28)
      - -Putman, Louise Day 1909, 1910 (Box 232.1, Folder 29)
      - -Russell, Anna 1908, 1908-1910 (Box 232.1, Folder 30)
      - -Sherman, Rose, 1910 (Box 232.1, Folder 31)
      - -Woman's National Farm and Garden Association, 1918 (Box 232.1, Folder 32)
      - -Women's Educational and Industrial Union, 1916-1918 (Box 232.1, Folder 33)
    - -Dedications
      - -Inscription on Steps
        [see Libraries-WANL-Photographs-Special Events-Dedication of Steps Inscription]
      - -Main Building, 1910 (Box 232.1, Folder 34)
      - -Naming, 1946 (Box 232.1, Folder 35)
      - -South Wing, 1962 (Box 232.1, Folder 36)
      - -WANL/Alumnae Gym Complex, 1982 (Box 232.1, Folder 37)
    - -Electronic Classroom, 1998-1999 (Box 232.1, Folder 38)
    - -Electronic Classroom-Specifications, 1999 (Box 232.1, Folder 39)
      [see also Flat File Drawer 8 (Appendix H)]
    - -Exhibits
      - -General, 1921- (Box 232.1, Folder 40)
      - -General (Box 232.1, Folder 41)
      - -500th Anniversary of Printing, 1940 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - -Fifty Books of Louis Silver, 1954 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - -Faculty Committee
      - -General, 1905-1907 (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - -General, 1920-1935 (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - -Minutes, 1905-1907 (Box 233, Folder 5)
      - -Secretary's Letter File, 1906-1907 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - -Faculty Offices, 1966- (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - -Fire, 1975 (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - -Funds (Building Funds)
      - -General, 1894-1908 (Box 233, Folder 9)
      - -Correspondence, 1907 (Box 233, Folder 10)
      - -Dr. Grace A. Preston Memorial, 1900 (Box 233, Folder 11)
      - -L. Clark Seelye Fund, 1898-1910 (Box 233, Folder 12)
      - -Statements and Receipts, 1909; undated (Box 233, Folder 13)
    - -Furnishings
      - -General, 1941-1981; undated (Box 233, Folder 14)
      - -Browsing Room, 1910-1915; 2000 (Box 233, Folder 15)
        [see also Libraries-WANL-Browsing Room]
      - -Clock, 1910-1912; undated (Box 233, Folder 16)
      - -Correspondence, 1909-1910 (Box 233, Folder 17)
      - -German Seminar Room, 1909-1912 (Box 233, Folder 18)
      - -Librarian's Office, 1909 (Box 233, Folder 19)
    - -Gifts and Acquisitions
      [see also Libraries-WANL-Accessions, Boxes 66-73]
      - -General, 1919-1918 (Box 233, Folder 20)
      - -General, 1930-1931 (Box 233, Folder 21)
      - -General, 1935-1939 (Box 233, Folder 22)
      - -General, 1940- (Box 233, Folder 23)
      - -Art and Artifacts, 1918-1930; undated (Box 233, Folder 24)
      - -Bible (13th Century ms), 1956 (Box 233, Folder 25)
      - -Delbosc Library, 1936 (Box 233, Folder 26)
      - -Forms and Procedures, 1946; undated (Box 233, Folder 27)
      - -Furniture, 1909-1936 (Box 233, Folder 28)
        [see also Libraries-WANL-Furnishings]
      - -Gift Request Slip, undated (Box 233, Folder 29)
      - -Hale Library, 1938 (Box 233, Folder 30)
      - -Memorial Gifts, 1906-1960 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - -Purchases, 1934-1939 (Box 234, Folder 2)
      - -Shakespeare Folios, 1961; undated (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - -Title II-A Grant, 1965 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - -Imports, 1915-1919 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - -Incunabula
      [see Libraries-WANL-Rare Book Room-Incunabula]
    - -Landscaping, 1993 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - -Lectures, Readings, and Conferences, 1925 (Box 234, Folder 7)
      [see also Libraries-Friends of the Library]
    - -Lexis-Nexis, 1998 (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - -Librarian's Reports, 1910- (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - -Library of Congress System, 1971 (Box 234, Folder 10)
    - -Microfilm and Reader, 1938-1940 (Box 234, Folder 11)
    - -Mortimer Rare Book Room
      [see Libraries-WANL-Rare Book Room]
    - -Multicultural Collection, 1993- (Box 234, Folder 12)
    - -Non-Print Resources Center (NPRC), 1988- (Box 234, Folder 13)
    - -Oral History Project, 1981 (Box 234, Folder 14)
    - -Pamphlets
      - -Informational Brochures, 1973-; undated (Box 234, Folder 15)
      - -Stack Location Directories, undated (Box 234, Folder 16)